Guide to Bess Reed papers 1901-1984
Montana Historical Society Research Center
- Dallas Reed, Sr.
  - Biographical Materials
    - Army Documents, 1917-1920, 1939-1941, 1952 (Box-folder 12 / 1)
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    - To John W. Reed, 1901-1902, 1907-1908 (Box-folder 12 / 2)
  - General Correspondence
    - Between Dallas Reed, Sr. and Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway Company, 1917-1922, 1937 (Box-folder 12 / 3)
    - Between Dallas Reed, Sr. and the National College of Chiropractic, 1923-1924, 1942 (Box-folder 12 / 4)
    - From Dorrance and Company Inc. (re publishing the manuscript "Nor Time Nor Space"), 1932 (Box-folder 12 / 5)
    - From United States Veterans' Administration (re transportation for medical treatment), 1933-1945 (Box-folder 12 / 6)
    - From United States Veterans' Bureau (re compensation), 1922-1929, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 12 / 7)
    - From Veterans' Welfare Commission, 1943 (Box-folder 12 / 8)
    - Regarding Funeral Information (correspondents include condolence letters and cremation papers), 1944 (Box-folder 12 / 9)
    - Regarding Railroad Retirement Board, 1937 (Box-folder 12 / 10)
    - Regarding Tri-Base Oil Company of Montana, 1935-1942 (Box-folder 12 / 11)